<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tayari</title><link>https://tayari.gg/</link><description>Recent content on Tayari</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 21:38:37 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tayari.gg/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Seamless Windows Applications in Linux</title><link>https://tayari.gg/guides/guides/cassowary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 21:38:37 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tayari.gg/guides/guides/cassowary/</guid><description>Introduction One frustration that every Linux user has experienced is when you need to run a particular program that is only available for Windows.
While for the overwhelming majority of applications there are equivalent solutions in Linux, sometimes the native Windows application is just what you need to use.
Whether it is because your professional workflow requires you to use it or the equivalent solutions are just not nearly as powerful as the original (looking at you Excel), there are times where your use case demands the Windows program.</description></item><item><title>Qubes OS - A Technical Introduction</title><link>https://tayari.gg/talks/qubes-technical-introduction/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 00:52:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tayari.gg/talks/qubes-technical-introduction/</guid><description>Introduction The fact that I daily drive Qubes OS on both my laptop and desktop and have been for over a year was something that piqued the curiosity of multiple people in the ASU Linux User's Group which prompted the request for me to present a talk on Qubes OS and not only how it works but what truly differentiates it.
In order to try to accommodate everyone regardless of technical knowledge, I started the presentation off with a general overview, mostly focusing on the user experience of Qubes before slowly diving deeper and deeper into its drivers and architecture and their respective technical details.</description></item><item><title>Resume</title><link>https://tayari.gg/resume/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 08:45:52 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tayari.gg/resume/</guid><description>Click here to view my resume in PDF form! About Me I am Daylam Tayari, a junior cybersecurity college student at Arizona State University and incoming penetration testing intern at Bishop Fox who is currently based in Phoenix, Arizona, United States. In my free time, I love working on various open source projects, enriching my cybersecurity skills, maintaining and improving my homelab and diving deeper in the Linux ecosystem.
I am an avid supporter of open source software and a privacy advocate, helping introduce people to better ways of protecting their personal privacy.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://tayari.gg/about/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 08:45:16 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tayari.gg/about/</guid><description>Introduction Welcome! This is my personal website where I post about anything from the myriad of topics that interest though as someone who is passionate about cybersecurity and the GNU/Linux ecosystem, those are primarily what the content of this site is going to revolve around. Nonetheless, I will certainly cover other matters that I particularly care about such as privacy, open source and free software, Qubes OS, digital rights, right to repair, self-hosting and setting up a homelab, geopolitics and more.</description></item><item><title>Nmap2Tex 0.1 Release</title><link>https://tayari.gg/projects/projects/nmap2tex-0.1-release/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 22:34:40 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tayari.gg/projects/projects/nmap2tex-0.1-release/</guid><description>Introduction What is Nmap2Tex? Well as it's name suggests, it converts a Nmap (a network scanner) scan result into a nicely pre-formatted LaTeX document containing all of the important information from the scan and also colour coding some components such as vulnerabilities according to their CVSS or hosts based on how vulnerable they are. The inspiration of this project really stems from my experience competing in the national Collegiate Cyber Defense (CCDC) competition, a collegiate cybersecurity competition which aims to help give students experience in a blue team environment, providing each team with a whole network infrastructure with everything from a firewall, a variety of both Linux and Windows machines and occasionally also VoIP devices.</description></item></channel></rss>