<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Daylam Tayari</title><link>https://tayari.gg/</link><description>Recent content on Daylam Tayari</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tayari.gg/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>TwitchRecover</title><link/><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 16:21:42 -0600</pubDate><guid/><description>&lt;p&gt;Tool with over 600K downloads which recovers and downloads all VODs, clips, streams, and highlights, including those are sub-only or deleted.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Transit Display</title><link/><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:50:35 -0600</pubDate><guid/><description>&lt;p&gt;An RGB LED matrix display that shows transit and commute ETAs using CTA, Divvy, and Transit app APIs.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Microsoft to Do Export</title><link/><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 16:04:35 -0600</pubDate><guid/><description>&lt;p&gt;A solution to export tasks and lists from Microsoft To Do into a Todoist or JSON format.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Nmap2tex</title><link/><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:55:56 -0600</pubDate><guid/><description>&lt;p&gt;Formatting tool that converts Nmap scans into a services, user, and vulnerability LaTeX report.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Pi Hole Blocklist</title><link/><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 16:07:43 -0600</pubDate><guid/><description>&lt;p&gt;Pi-hole blocklist that compiles millions of trackers, advertisements, spams, and fishing domains.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Dotfiles</title><link/><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:36:56 -0600</pubDate><guid/><description>&lt;p&gt;A compilation of my configurations for my shell environment and various programs I use on a daily basis.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Seamless Windows Applications in Linux</title><link>https://tayari.gg/guides/cassowary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 21:38:37 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tayari.gg/guides/cassowary/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="introduction"&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One frustration that every Linux user has experienced is when you need to run a particular program that is only available for Windows.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While for the overwhelming majority of applications there are equivalent solutions in Linux, sometimes the native Windows application is just what you need to use.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether it is because your professional workflow requires you to use it or the equivalent solutions are just not nearly as powerful as the original (looking at you Excel), there are times where your use case demands the Windows program.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Qubes OS - A Technical Introduction</title><link>https://tayari.gg/talks/qubes-technical-introduction/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 00:52:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tayari.gg/talks/qubes-technical-introduction/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="introduction"&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The fact that I daily drive Qubes OS on both my laptop and desktop and have been for over a year was something that piqued the curiosity of multiple people in the ASU Linux User's Group which prompted the request for me to present a talk on Qubes OS and not only how it works but what truly differentiates it.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In order to try to accommodate everyone regardless of technical knowledge, I started the presentation off with a general overview, mostly focusing on the user experience of Qubes before slowly diving deeper and deeper into its drivers and architecture and their respective technical details.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Nmap2Tex Release</title><link>https://tayari.gg/articles/nmap2tex-release/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 22:34:40 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://tayari.gg/articles/nmap2tex-release/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="introduction"&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What is Nmap2Tex? Well as it's name suggests, it converts a Nmap (a network scanner) scan result into a nicely pre-formatted LaTeX document containing all of the important information from the scan and also colour coding some components such as vulnerabilities according to their CVSS or hosts based on how vulnerable they are.&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;
The inspiration of this project really stems from my experience competing in the national Collegiate Cyber Defense (CCDC) competition, a collegiate cybersecurity competition which aims to help give students experience in a blue team environment, providing each team with a whole network infrastructure with everything from a firewall, a variety of both Linux and Windows machines and occasionally also VoIP devices. &lt;br/&gt;
Throughout this competition, we must execute injects (task requests by the organisers) all while being constantly attacked by a professional red team and having to perform the respective incident response.&lt;br/&gt;
One particular inject that is present in every competition and which is requested in the beginning stages of the competition is a network inventory. In this report, we must include every device running on the network, their information (OS, hostname, IP) and the list of open ports and their respective services but also the list of vulnerabilities present on each machine on the system.&lt;br/&gt;
We usually rely on using Nmap to scan the network and retrieve all necessary information for the report.&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;
Now at one recent invitational, I was tasked with performing this inject and let me just say that manually typing up the results of a Nmap scan on around a dozen devices, each running a large number of services, is incredibly frustrating to say the least which is exacerbated by how time intensive it is.&lt;br/&gt;
It was while completing that inject that I made the decision that I would never again let myself complete this inject in such a painstaking way, let alone let someone else on my team also suffer through this.&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;
Since Nmap has an option to output into XML and due to my fondness for LaTeX, I decided that I would build a tool that would take in the Nmap scan result in an XML format and then convert it into a nicely formatted LaTeX document based on a provided template.&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;
This is the result of that, here releasing version 0.1 which contains full support for Nmap network scan and vulnerability scan conversions among other things.&lt;br/&gt;
Version 0.1 is the initial version of the program and it's version number will continue to increase until I release version 1.0 when I am satisfied with the project and it's state.&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;To download the release:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://github.com/daylamtayari/Nmap2Tex/releases/tag/v0.1"&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://tayari.gg/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tayari.gg/about/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="introduction"&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Welcome!&lt;/strong&gt; I am Daylam Tayari, an experienced penetration testing consultant at &lt;a href="https://bishopfox.com"&gt;Bishop Fox&lt;/a&gt; who also has development experience across both my professional career and my free time, working on a multitude of open-source tools. Across my penetration testing experience, I have worked with a multitude of industry-leading clients to best address their security concerns and performed network, application, and cloud penetration tests as well as secure code reviews.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I enjoy developing tools and programs across both my professional career and my free time. Go has been my language of choice for some time however, also well experienced with Python, Java, and to a lesser extent C++, Rust, and JavaScript.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>